Ghayas Abou Fakher

Date of Birth: 20/04/1992

Marital Status : Married

Resident : Iraq - Erbil

Call & Whatsapp: +964-3593641

Email: yasoo.af@gmail.com

Passport Number: N012404134



Work History

Programming and operating systems teacher | Syrian high school (9/2012 - 7/2014)

Responsibilities

- Teaching computer and software technologies.
- Teaching maintenance and upgrade of computer hardware.
- Teaching programming language (C#, HTML, Visual basic).

Computer teacher | SB Overseas Belgium Organization for refugees LEBANON (2/2016 - 7/2019)

Responsibilities

- Give instructions to students in the learning of materials and equipment.
- Teach basic topics such as Microsoft Office, Software, and Hardware.
- Monitor the performance of students regularly.

IT support | Ghia Holding company LEBANON (1/2015 - 11/2019) Responsibilities

- Responsible for hardware and software installation, maintenance and repair.
- Maintaining the company IT systems.
- Reporting to the IT Director.
- Managing the internal & hosted network infrastructure including: servers ,switches ,telephony.

Training for 1month | Areeba financial technology for payment solutions

Training for 2month | Takchgroup internet service provider LEBANON.

Education

Syrian Virtual University

Bachelor of Information Technology

Graduated

Syria

Computer Technology Institute

• Diploma of Computer Technologies

Graduated

Syria

Computer Technology High School

Graduated

Syria

Languages

ARABIC

Native

ENGLISH

Fluent writing and reading

Summary

Over 4 years of experience as a Computer Teacher, is now looking to obtain a position where my extensive experience can be utilized to expand my Duties in order to move up to a high-level position within the company.

Personal Skill

SKILL	Evaluation 5 🛠
IT	***
Programming	***
HTML , C# , JS	
Networking	***
Database	***
Microsoft	***
Excel,Access,Word	

References

Ghia Holding Company SB Overseas Takchgroup ISP

Available upon request